[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What used to be the currency of Italy?",
   "Answer": "Lira"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "In what country was pesetas the currency?",
   "Answer": "Spain"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Which country is the largest producer of olive oil?",
   "Answer": "Spain"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "What is the world s largest office building?",
   "Answer": "Pentagon"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "Which currency is at home on the Johannesburg Stock Exchange?",
   "Answer": "South African rand"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "What is the main component in glass?",
   "Answer": "Sand"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Which country is the origin of the car brands Daewoo and Kia?",
   "Answer": "South Korea"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "Where does a car with the letters CH come from?",
   "Answer": "Switzerland"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "What is the national currency of Albania?",
   "Answer": "Albanese lek"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "What is the national airline of Australia?",
   "Answer": "Qantas"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "In which military camp is the US gold reserve stored?",
   "Answer": "Fort Knox"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "What is the national currency of Laos?",
   "Answer": "Laos Kip"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "Which prehistoric animal does also indicate a large tanker?",
   "Answer": "Mammoth"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "What is the brand of the oldest sewing machines?",
   "Answer": "Singer"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "Where was built the first subway?",
   "Answer": "In London"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "Between which two places did the first railway track in the UK run?",
   "Answer": "Stockton to Darlington"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "In which country is Varig Airlines based?",
   "Answer": "Brazil"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "What is Pakistan s currency?",
   "Answer": "Rupee"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "How many digits does an IBAN number consist of?",
   "Answer": "Fourteen digits"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What is the official currency in Nepal?",
   "Answer": "Rupee"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "Which Japanse car brand did exist from 1932 until 1983?",
   "Answer": "Datsun"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "What is the biggest oil company in the United States?",
   "Answer": "Exxon Mobil"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "Which company was establised in the year 1962 by Sam Walton and is one of the biggest employers in the world?",
   "Answer": "Walmart"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "Which Italian family is in charge of FIAT?",
   "Answer": "Agnelli"
 },
 {
   "No": 25,
   "Quiz question": "What was the currency of Greece before the introduction of the EURO?",
   "Answer": "Drachme"
 }
]